Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Hello, hello?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Welcome back to the day.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Welcome to our live training. Hey, Mary. Hey, Adele, how are you doing?
Mary Chalhoub: Doing good.
Adele Best: Thanks, how are you?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Wonderful. I, I got hit with just a terrible cold on…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Thursday. Today is the day that I've actually felt the best I have in 4 days, so… I've gotten a lot of sleep, which is good. I'll tell ya, we, we have a routine in our house where it just… it works great for us. My wife…
Jeremiah Krakowski: goes to bed, the kids go down, they sleep in our room, and I clean up the house at night. I clean up, I'll do all the dishes, I do all the… just everything, so they wake up, and the house is just…
Jeremiah Krakowski: all organized and put up, and that's not even, like, a good… like, a main skill of mine. My wife is super skilled at that. But I have literally…
Jeremiah Krakowski: rewired myself to be able to do that every night, because my wife is also… her love language is act of ser… acts of service, and so it's just… it's just a way that I can each… each day, reduce her stress and help our house and all that. All that to say, I've been feeling…
Jeremiah Krakowski: this cold, and… so the dishes did not get done. They got… they got done, like, 2 nights ago, but I didn't basically do them for, like, 4 days. And so, finally, last night, like, I did everything, it was all… it was all good, and… but, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I was like, I was…
Adele Best: She noticed. I bet she noticed the lack… the lack of clean dishes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, well, no, I was… no, honestly, it was like, I had to talk with her. I'm like, hey, listen, they're not gonna get done, because I need to go to sleep, I need to rest, I need to get some rest. And we were up late both of those nights with the kids, with different things that we had to… that we had to do, so it was just like, okay, like, I need sleep. I'm not gonna… I'm not going to get well if I'm only sleeping, you know, like, 2 hours. So…
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, okay, sure, no worries on that. Anyways, what I want to do today is a couple of things. You know, I've been talking about this on my social media. We've been going over all this stuff with AI agents and all that, but what I've been doing now, and I love this, is I got them all set up with,
Jeremiah Krakowski: a lot of the different, like, tools that are out there don't work well with AI agents, and a lot of these tools are actually designed to not work well with AI agents. Like…
Adele Best: Oh.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Otter AI, for instance.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that hits all my transcripts. The agents have a really hard time pulling those transcripts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, that's Otter AI. I have a tool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Cold.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Transcript AI, That my agents built me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That is fully set, set up right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Seamlessly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What's my login for it?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Should be this one here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, so what it is, is it is a version of Otter.ai, that's not it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'll poop. I forget what the… oh, you know what? It's probably this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Probably this email.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I just wanna… I just wanna show you guys this. Yeah, here we go. So this is a version of… and my agents built this in, like, a day. I was making a version of it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: it was not that great. The one I was making, my agents did this in, like, a day and made it way better.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So now it has all my, like, call transcripts and everything that we're doing live.
Jeremiah Krakowski: in here. See, this one says failed, so I could try to re… retry it. Probably… probably might be having some trouble with that one, but it might be because we deleted the recording. So it pulls all my recordings out of… out of, Zoom.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then there's an API that connects so the agents can just download each transcript.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and use it, and then my team members can download it, and then I have these little content generation workflows right here, where off of each transcript, we can generate a call summary, call prep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: content summary, blog posts, weekly bullet points, all that. So there's a whole content studio built into it from the transcripts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which is really, really cool. I can upload a transcript, I can record it, and this is just… literally, the agents went and built this, because now they just have to connect through an API to get all those transcripts. And the beauty of this is.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This week, I was able to have a vision that I had, where my agents created me, last night, 5 PDFs.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for today's call. So what they did was, and this is just… this is just something like the power of AI. I just want to show you guys this before we go into the training.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is the PDFs…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where's my Zoom window?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where'd Zoom go? Oh, there it is. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Cool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: WCA calls, okay, so PDF number one, it's like a weekly brief, where kind of it analyzed the last couple of weeks' calls, just all the questions that were asked on the calls. This is like a raw
Jeremiah Krakowski: VDF.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Of course, I was able to pull in all the transcripts, 85,000 words.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Almost 500 hours of content, 12 core frameworks that we talked about.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I don't know that I had 12 core frameworks, I don't know that, you know, we're doing a full list, and all the different questions that everybody had, and all that is in there. Okay, so then I dove in, and I'm like, okay, tell me what to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Give me 5 teaching angles for, this week, like, what I want to teach this week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right here, okay? Make me a combo outline of angles 1 and 5.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, so now what this did was it made me, like, a whole kind of outline of what we want to talk about here today, and then I went deeper, I said, can you take a step back, do deep psychoanalysis of each member, their questions, as far as the deeper issue, question behind the question, what they've been dealing with each week?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I was like, okay, going deep on this one.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Members analysis, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so this is about each member right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: information about, like, what they're… what they're going through, stuff like that. Like, there's Adele right there. Brilliant visionary.
Adele Best: I was gonna say, what does it say about me?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Great visionary trapped in perpetual planning mode.
Adele Best: That sounds about right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Surface Problem. Present on all three calls, has a clear vision.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know… well, I guess you do have your lovable account set up right there, but…
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: actually built her first draft in Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: proud of it, but acknowledged I didn't have as much time as I wanted, question upon the question. They orbit around removing yourself in the process. How can I build a successful business?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Vulnerability and exposure feel dangerous.
Jeremiah Krakowski: She explicitly says she doesn't want to be the face, okay? If I'm visible, I'll be judged. If I'm judged, I'll be hurt. That's the underlying belief system.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And these are all things that, like, again, you don't need to necessarily, like, fix these right away, but it just gives me, as a coach, and it gives…
Adele Best: Pointers, it's good pointers, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: good pointers as far as what's going on. Like, one of the things that I've learned as a coach
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's not my job to say, hey, you're doing this wrong, and you need to change it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I feel like there's a lot of coaches who try to do that, and they miss a lot of nuance as far as, like, why somebody's doing what they're doing.
Adele Best: Yeah, it's more to ask the questions or reflect, isn't it? To reflect back.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And when I'm doing a group coaching program, it's different, because if I'm in one-on-one coaching, I'm talking a lot less.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If I'm in a group program, I'm talking a lot more.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So how do I talk a lot more, but still provide that reflection? That's the biggest kind of thing that I… that I need to do. And then I had it create me, like, a coach's toolkit, 15 things I might not have known, things I… that I might not realize as I'm coaching my clients, ways to help them through different patterns and things like that.
Adele Best: Oh, that's really good.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, so what's cool is, like, then I told my agents, okay, make this a repeatable skill every Sunday.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You go through the calls, and you make… and you do this for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So now I don't have to prompt the agents to do this. Every Sunday, they're gonna automatically do what we… what I just showed you.
Adele Best: That's amazing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna have output of these PDFs every Sunday.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For my client calls.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now, what was interesting was I used to manually… I would take almost 2 hours a week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I would prompt ChatGPT and Claude and all of those to do this exact thing right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Manually. I would take all the transcripts, and I would manually bring them in and do that. And so it's just like, like, right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The reduction in stress In being able to show up on these calls is just… exponentially.
Jeremiah Krakowski: beyond what I… what I imagined, being able to do this. Now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: again, I showed you guys kind of how you can set up your own open claw agents. I'm gonna be helping people set those up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the reason why… now, I mentioned my wife's mom broke her leg, a week ago.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then we were sick last week, so it was, like, all the progress that I had planned on doing last week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But we do have a prototype that I'm testing right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What I want to actually test out is instead of you guys having to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Set up your own API keys, and set up your own agents, and do all of this. I want the agents set up and ready to go, where all you do is you make an account, and then you can chat with it right away.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… and that's what I… because I feel like that's more valuable than me just setting up a server for you, is actually creating a system that's ready to go and ready to plug into within minutes of you signing up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it's taking a little bit longer to set that up, but I've already noticed, like, a couple competitors are out there in the marketing space that are offering this same kind of thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so I'm like, okay, I gotta get this going, and I want to offer it to different industries. Like, one of the things is there's a big analysis that's been going around of industries that are not using AI at all. You could literally create them open claw agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and sell this to them at, like, 3 times the premium of what I might sell in an industry that's already using AI. You know, an agent for a construction company could easily sell that for $497 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or $297 a month, or $197 a month for even just a basic level agent. And so, those are just some things that I've been exploring and doing. Now, today, today's teaching, what I want to go into today, and this is why, again.
Jeremiah Krakowski: this AI agent stuff, It's important, and it's relevant for you to learn.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The two biggest things that I would just recommend for AI agents, again, lovable, start… go make a lovable account, just like how I was telling y'all to make a ChatGPT account.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Go make a lovable account, because it can create little micro-software tools and things like that for you, that you can use that can automate different tasks that you might have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, I made an advertising tool that creates me ad graphics. I made me a tool that creates social media posts inside of Lovable, and I can create my landing pages as well inside of here. So this is one of the fastest ways that you can get up and running with agents, is by using Lovable as one of them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then again, Manus, right here. Now, Manus has a really cool AI agent that's kind of like OpenClaw that they've offered, called Agents, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that you can use, you can click this Agents tab right inside of Manus.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it's kind of like a slightly less powerful version of OpenClaw, which is really cool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay? Now, one of the things that Manus just launched today…
Jeremiah Krakowski: In their connected apps, Look at this!
Jeremiah Krakowski: Meta Ads Manager.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Wasn't I talking about this?
Adele Best: So they knew that we were gonna… they knew that we were gonna use this for that, then?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, Meta purchased Manus, remember?
Adele Best: Yeah, yeah, yeah. So they had brought it in mind with the idea of us using it like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Didn't I say 3 weeks ago that they're gonna add in a feature to run all your Facebook ads through Banus?
Adele Best: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's exactly what this is.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I've been reading on X, they just launched this this morning, by the way, so I've not been able to, like, test it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But, like, right there, I just gave it access to all of my ad accounts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now let's go in here, help me test the connector.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And Manus is gonna go into my ads accounts and go test if it's connected. Got it. I'll test the connector, I'll start reading the relevant skill and listing available tools. So, what I have seen people basically say is that it can analyze your ads.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It can help you manage your ads, it can help you upload your ads, run your ads.
Jeremiah Krakowski: literally as an all-in-one agent tool right here inside of Manus. So if anything, like, you want help running your ads.
Jeremiah Krakowski: activating this little meta ads manager tool right here, and then you just talk to it like ChatGPT.
Adele Best: That's incredible, but what if you haven't ran any ads yet, and there's no data for it to go in?
Jeremiah Krakowski: It doesn't need the data to go on, because it's trained on the best practices of running ads. Okay, brilliant. So I'm gonna have to analyze all of my ad accounts right here.
Adele Best: That is really powerful, because it knows the algorithm better than we do. It does, exactly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, it's amazing. So I'm going in here, I'm having to analyze just all of my different ad campaigns that are either paused or turned on.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What's running right now?
Jeremiah Krakowski: different ad spend, clicks, all of it. So, anyways, we're not gonna go over this right now, because I need to play around with it, but what I have seen people say is that it'll literally, like, help you upload your ads, it'll help you come up with the ad ideas, launch your campaigns, create all your creatives, literally all of that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: can be done inside of Manus right here. You just… you just give it your landing page, tell it, make me, 10 different ad variations with graphics that are made with Nano Banana, upload them to 3 of my best targeting groups, and it'll probably literally launch the campaign.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna go test it out with my new campaign. I just finished.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the recording of and everything. I have a brand new campaign. So I don't have a campaign right now for AI agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because I wanted to get this one launched first. This is kind of my, like, bridge offer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to my audience.
Jeremiah Krakowski: On this… oh, I want to show you guys something really, really cool in just a second, too.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see. Yes, this is my bridge offer, the non-techy AI Video Content Creation Guide, 5 minutes. How to use AI to create content is the whole idea behind it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, I made this offer back in December, haven't launched it, finally recorded the webinar.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so I'll be launching this this week, and I'll have, Manus do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I actually went ahead, so this is my mom's website right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a realchange.com.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay? This is my website right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And in 2 days, I had my agents rebuild both of them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is the brand new version of Jeremiah Krakowski.com that's coming soon.
Adele Best: Oh, I love that. That's really good, Jeremiah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: rebuilt from the ground up. So my agents can write my blog posts for me. Look, it has infinite scroll on
Jeremiah Krakowski: Blog post, so the blog post just keeps scrolling.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It has all… it has my podcast episodes all loaded into it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That you can listen to, that you can watch. It's connected with all the right podcast stuff. It's connected to all my offers already. And then we did the same thing, for my mom's. Hers was a little bit…
Jeremiah Krakowski: kind of almost here already. It's not much different, but we added more of these little, like, features.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To it, different feature sections.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To make brand new sites. We did that in a day. I did that in a day while I was watching my kids last week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I had the agents build at both sites.
Adele Best: Can you just literally tell it, insert testimonial section? Boom.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I actually just told it, look at ARealChange.com, rebuild it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Look at Jeremiah Krakowski.com and rebuild it.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then one of the things I did was I told it, okay, make me 10 design examples of how you would redesign each of these sites.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then what I did was I actually went through, like I went to Designer, we went through 40 different, iterations of design changes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To come up with the designs, like, for my site.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Off of the initial version of it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: it was pretty cool, I just… I just treated the agent like I was working with a… with a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: With an actual marketing agency, and did all that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, again, getting up and running with these agents is one of the biggest things that you can do, but what I want to talk about is kind of what comes before that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: what comes before that? Because, again, I understand the… the technical… overwhelm…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I didn't see the live in the Facebook group unless… oh, yeah, the live… it's not live in the Facebook group, you're absolutely right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So let me go live in the Facebook group and get this… get this going right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's not opening up. Go live.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Custom streaming service. Here we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There we go, the Facebook group.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We'll go in the group here…
Jeremiah Krakowski: is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: me kind of showing you guys those different examples of what I'm doing with the agents, is that helpful?
Adele Best: Yeah, definitely. Yep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because it's kind of… it's kind of giving you the ideas of, like, you don't need to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Figure it all out on your own.
Adele Best: Yeah, definitely. It's a super helpful, fast way to get a landing page together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, not just getting a landing page together, like, running your whole business.
Adele Best: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, totally.
Dorothy: Yeah, I mean, I find there's so much to do with my website, constantly. It needs updating, tweaking, nursing. It's just, there's so much at the moment that needs updating on my website.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And, yeah.
Dorothy: countless.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so that's what I did, was I just, I literally told the agent, like, okay, set me up a new server.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's like, okay, go sign up for an account at Hetzner.com.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, the agent walked me through this. It sent me to this site called Hetzner.com. I had to do research on different servers. I was like, okay, sign up for an account, put your credit card in, and I'll go make the server for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, it was just…
Jeremiah Krakowski: awesome, because I don't… I'm not going to give my agent my credit card, but I gave it access to be able to create
Jeremiah Krakowski: Servers on my behalf, for instance.
Dorothy: What would you suggest, Jeremiah, as the first things to ask an agent to do?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Whatever… this is great, I saw a video about this the other week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Anything that you do in your business that needs to be done, that takes up
Jeremiah Krakowski: More of your time than you want to do doing it.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And…
Jeremiah Krakowski: things that you have VAs that… that are doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: but also things that, like, VAs can't do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, it's really just, like, the first things is, like, building… an offloading actions that…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Take up your time that are necessary for your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So one of the things was, like, my agents could not use Squarespace.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The way Squarespace is built is for people to click on things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the way the agents work is they go into the code and they kind of find where the buttons are and stuff like that, and it was nearly impossible for the agents to use Squarespace.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's why I was like, okay, rebuild my whole Squarespace site.
Adele Best: That's validating, because it was practically impossible for me as well.
Jeremiah Krakowski: rebuild my Squarespace site in a way that agents can use to quickly make me landing pages, and all of that, so now, once I launch that site, my agents can spin up a new page, or 5 pages, in seconds for me.
Dorothy: Yeah, because I've got so much to do with the music side of my business, because I've got yoga and music on the one website.
Dorothy: Because I've got two dual businesses, and so that's a whole thing of, like, how to set up… I've got to update all my music.
Dorothy: Ready for promoting and going to venues.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's… I would say that's one of the biggest things that, that,
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think it's stopping, like, most people from being able to get their business off the ground, is all the stuff for setting up the funnels and the emails and all of that, and if you could just outsource and automate all of that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now you can, like, after you kind of get over the dopamine hit of… because there's a huge dopamine hit.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and having agents do this stuff for you. It's like dopamine crack, I will tell you that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's like, you know… Like, I… my mom had to almost call me out on it a little bit. She was like, okay, I think you're getting a little bit addicted to agent dopamine.
Adele Best: Yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The last, like…
Adele Best: It's a bit high the last few days.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know, unless, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: being productive, and I'm like, okay, great. No, like, that's a good call-out, Mom. She called me out on that, like, 2 weeks ago. And so what I've shifted is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm only having my agents do stuff
Jeremiah Krakowski: that makes me productive in what I am doing in our businesses.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Currently. That's it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm going a little bit slower on the stuff that is not directly related to my business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it's been the thing that saved me this past week, because I've not worked hardly at all this last week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: With my wife being out of the house, and me having to wash the kids with her… her mom's broken hip.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's given me the ability to
Jeremiah Krakowski: be present with my kids, and still have my business progress forward.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's what I think is so cool about this, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, but the thing is that I think that we need to make sure of… is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: That we can go through, and we can get this stuff done Quickly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Without taking a lot of time to get it… to get it accomplished.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and go through this. We've talked about, like, the pricing of your $5 offer. We've talked about how having a $5 offer sends better signals to the algorithm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We've talked about how, like, it's easier for somebody to spend $5 than spending more than that, and once somebody spends $5, they trust you more.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Overall, to spend more money with you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you run a… if you run a funnel, let's say you do it for $10 a day, that's 300 bucks a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The cost to get a $5 purchase might be 5 to 10 bucks.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So if you get, say, 100 people, That's $500 in revenue.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that might be $200 in profit over your ad spend.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If 20% of those people upgrade to a $75 a month community, that's $1,500 a month in recurring revenue, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: If 5% of them Then upgrade to, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a $297 group, or something like that, that's another $1,500 right there. So those would be, like, two levels right there that you could do. You could do kind of, like, a low ticket and a mid ticket.
Jeremiah Krakowski: type of an offer with these $5 offers. And so now your initial ad spend, you spent $300 to $500 in ads, you brought in about…
Jeremiah Krakowski: $3,000, $4,000 in sales.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which is maybe about a 10 to 12X return.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then you have those recurring buyers, where now each month you have recurring revenue, and then you compound that on top of it. Now, this is one of the things that I think that, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In business, it's not about what you're making in one month, it's how it compounds together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because if you're getting, say, an additional $1,500 in revenue.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you do that consistently over the course of 12 months.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And let's say you're losing $500 each month, so it's a net. When I say losing, it's like in cancellations, that's like a 30%. For every new… for every 3 people you're getting new, you're losing 1 person each month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's how that math works out.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it's a net of $1,000 a month. After 12 months, your business is making $12,000 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's the type of math, again, that these types of business models do, and that's why consistently showing up, the only way that any of us are going to show up consistently
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's by us not doing all the work anymore.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is by us not needing to be the one that has to come up with all the ideas for our offers.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And again, the best way that I do this is, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: By having an agent that can ingest all my content.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, for Tiffany, I would take all the transcripts of every podcast that she's done.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would get them all transcribed.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I would put those into an agent that can review them and start to build out
Jeremiah Krakowski: all the content that she's posting have a content machine that gives her daily content ideas, and she can choose one or two of those. What I've been posting on my social media the last, like, couple of days, I… I'll tell you this, when I'm going through a hard time in my life.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Posting on social media is very hard for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So my wife's mom broke her hip, all that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I put a pause on posting on my social media for about…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You see, how many days was it?
Jeremiah Krakowski: About 6 days. I didn't post on my Instagram for 6 days.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Till… till she got home.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then, the post that I've been posting
Jeremiah Krakowski: Are literally ideas that my agents gave me to post.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So my agents gave me the idea, I ran with it, and I'll tell you, these videos are getting, like, 3, 5, 700, even a thousand views.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Off of the ideas that my agents are giving me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: off of my content, off of what we're talking about, off of doing competitive analysis with competitors. So you can have an agent that then goes out there, Tiffany, and finds who are the 10 people that are doing exactly what you're doing as well.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And finding what are they doing as far as content goes. In fact, Tiffany, I just want to show you… let's just do a fun example of this right now, live.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Tiffany Quinones?
Tiffany Quinones: Present!
Jeremiah Krakowski: What's up, girl?
Tiffany Quinones: Hey!
Jeremiah Krakowski: Podcast.
Tiffany Quinones: Now, again, this doesn't have all your…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Podcast transcripts, because there's a lot more you talk about than just
Jeremiah Krakowski: The titles of your episodes, right?
Tiffany Quinones: Cru-correct.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But what we can do is just to get kind of a bird's eye view here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna go through all your episodes that go all the way back to October… oh, August, June, May, March. Okay, let's see, let's go back to… let's go back all the way to last year.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Through last year.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And we're gonna pull this up into a text file…
Adele Best: Are you sharing the screen?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Not yet. I will, in just a sec.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There's not much to show on screen right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm just copying all the text from her podcast.
Jeremiah Krakowski: into a window.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I'm gonna pull that into my…
Tiffany Quinones: Jill? Agent Jill?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, Agent Jill, she's the research agent.
Tiffany Quinones: Oh, speaking of, would you be willing to share with me
Tiffany Quinones: what you're bringing up, because, I started implementing a little bit of what I remember from last week, but I liked Agent Jill. She's amazing. Awesome. Awesome employee you have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright, let's see, this is… I'm just gonna save that right there, we're gonna call it…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Take this info about… Tiffany's… podcast, and I want you to do some…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Competitive social media analysis, just like you do for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Top trends in her industry… News, articles, posts, ideas for content that is trending today related to her topic.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So right there, what it is, is it's actually looking at what's out there
Jeremiah Krakowski: In the world that you're not posting, but that, say, other people that have the similar message to you are posting.
Tiffany Quinones: Hmm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and then we merge that with your content ideas. So it's competitor analysis of your niche.
Tiffany Quinones: Combined with…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Those, those different ideas.
Jeremiah Krakowski: My mother-in-law is doing much better. She's at home, and she's doing exercises and getting stronger each day, so…
Tiffany Quinones: Good.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We're gonna go see her this evening. But anyway, so that's what the agent is doing right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's one of the things that I would do. For… for Mary, for instance, I would have her load up all her funnels, all of her… any coaching courses. Again, these are transcripts, her books.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Into an agent, and then have it review all of that to come up with, like, 3…
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, 3 ideas for new funnels that she could create, have the agent go ahead and create those funnels. Same for you, Tiffany, I'd have you go… have the agents go and create
Jeremiah Krakowski: Give you 3 ideas for funnels that you could create, and then go build them for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: One thing you could do… now, this is really cool… because you're using Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could tell… you could, you could, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: tell an agent, like, okay, I'm using Levable to build out the landing pages, give me a prompt to give Levable to build out this whole funnel.
Tiffany Quinones: Mmm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then the agent will literally give you a prompt to copy and paste into Lovable to build the funnel.
Tiffany Quinones: That's what I'm talking about. Simplicity.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Cool.
Tiffany Quinones: My word for the year is simplicity, so…
Jeremiah Krakowski: For Dorothy, again, taking all of, kind of, Dorothy's landing pages, offers, recording transcripts of what she's doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Adele, I just… I think that transcripts is such a powerful thing, that's why I wanna…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I want to take my, transcript app that I've been… I've been… had my agents make, and I want to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I wanna… Possibly offer it to you guys, as well, that you can use for your transcripts, too.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because it's just so valuable to have.
Adele Best: Could I load my book? Could I load my book into it and tell it to create…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Put your book into it, all that, whether if it's PDF, EPUB, any of those formats, it can load into.
Dorothy: So, when it's building out a funnel, do you need to have, like, specific software for that?
Dorothy: So, like, you've already got the backend ready, and you say, go in, use this software to build the funnel.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, so for doing… so for doing a funnel.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's where Lovable is so valuable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because Lovable can build the whole funnel for you.
Dorothy: I see, so it would have everything within it, like the sort of the email follow-up, and, you know…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can build your whole website even inside of Lovable.
Dorothy: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because I was originally doing just a draft of Sandy's whole site here, and lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then we can build out, like, the whole… the whole funnel, all the pages. We have her whole health bot right here built inside of Lovable. Every page.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To it is on here.
Adele Best: Where does she host her community?
Jeremiah Krakowski: What?
Adele Best: Does she have a community place where there's, like, pre-recordings, like Teachable, like you have?
Jeremiah Krakowski: She has the community in, Tribe platform, which is
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would say one of the worst platforms that's out there that exists. Oh, I've never heard of it. Would not recommend using it. I'm gonna have my agents probably build me their own version of, like, Thinkific, or…
Jeremiah Krakowski: School for my business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But…
Adele Best: Save so much money.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, exactly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But, I think School, or Thinkific, or Teachable, those 3 are great.
Adele Best: Yes, I really love skill.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, I actually… I actually think instead of Thinkific today, I think… I'm on Thinkific.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would say Teachable is probably a little better.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Today, Because they've kept themselves up to speed with AI tools and all those different things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They've just… they've made… they've done a lot better job of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: piecing all those things together, and then school, yeah, school is another just great community for… Building communities, and…
Jeremiah Krakowski: and creating those. So, both of those, you kind of build your community inside of either Teachable or School.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is what I would say would be great.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yep. But then here's the thing that you can do, again, so let's say I have my open claw agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You set it up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you can… yeah, Mary, I'll go… I'll go over that as well here in just a sec.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We've been talking about it for probably the last 2 months now, because everything's shifted in that world.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I'll talk about that in just a moment. I'll just do kind of a recap on agents. So I think we'll… I think we'll need to just do that each time as we have new people coming on, because it really is cutting edge. It's a new way of using the internet and using…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Everything that we're doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: My agents…
Jeremiah Krakowski: can log in to Thinkific.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and upload videos and download them from Zoom.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And let's say the video file's too big, because Thinkific has a 2GB video limit. My agents can then compress the video down to 2GB using FFmpeg.
Jeremiah Krakowski: it can then upload the video, it can then… it'll then create the course lesson inside of Thinkific for me. It'll… it can do all of that, the same way that a VA does.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it's because I've been able to give my agents the skills
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can… these are… these are… skills are things that you can download and install.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So my agents have the skills of computer use, so they can use a mouse and keyboard the same way a person can.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so what the agent does is it takes screenshots of, okay, what's on screen, it can click on things, and then it'll take another screenshot, it'll click on those things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, that's where it's like, no matter what tool you're using, whether it's school or all of that, you could have your agent set up your whole school community.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You have your agent set up, your whole Thinkific, your whole…
Jeremiah Krakowski: That. So, okay, back to, like, what is an agent? Let's just give kind of a bird's-eye view on this, because we've been talking about this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So we are… and every news outlet is talking about this right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We have left.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I don't think most people realize this, the chatbot era of AI.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We've been talking about using tools like ChatGPT and Claude and Poe and all those.
Jeremiah Krakowski: now, We are entering, because we're not fully here yet, we're in a transition period.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And the sooner you can learn this stuff, the better, of fully agent-based workflows.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where anything that you can do on a computer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Anything that you would do to manage your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is done by telling an AI agent
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or team of agents what to do, the same way that you would tell a human virtual assistant.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And the beauty of AI agents is that they have unlimited memory, that learns
Jeremiah Krakowski: everything about what you're doing, it can download as many files and information about your business. So, like, for instance, I don't have to give my agent the transcripts to all of my coaching calls. It just goes and gets them on its own.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I don't have to upload these things, even. I just tell them what to do, and they go and do it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm having my agents rebuild a lot of the expensive software.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In my business. I've already saved, I think, like, $300 a month in software so far.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I'll probably be able… I'll probably be able to knock out almost $1,000 worth of software.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And replace it with just… just agents doing everything.
Dorothy: What's the website that you suggested, Jeremiah, that's the one where you don't have to pay a huge amount for it? It's a German one.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's a… that's for servers, it's called Hetzner.
Dorothy: Oh, right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's… so that… so those are just for, like, raw…
Dorothy: I still need… because I've got GoDaddy, a GoDaddy Daddy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, so those are just, like, raw…
Dorothy: No.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Those are, like, raw computer servers.
Dorothy: Boom.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like… if I'm setting up an agent, there's actually something that popped on the scene, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: because I'm reading all this stuff on X, I'm telling you, I'm like, I'm… every night, I'm just reading on agents every night on X.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So these tools popped in the scene. These are… this is $250 on Amazon.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is a 16GB mini PC that you could run, like, 10 agents on.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that could sit in your office right here. So you don't need a Mac Mini, you could use this, it's like $250.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you can run your agent right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now, if you do a server, the server cost might be $15 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so that's, like, what… that's, like, what the raw server cost might be.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then you also still need API tokens.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you would need a Claude Max account, or a ChatGPT Pro account.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, for instance, at Claude… Claude AI.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I give it my token for my max plan right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because… because the agent software… Still needs a brain.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so this is 20 times usage right here. You can get a Claude Max account.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's about $200 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So there is a cost to having these agents do everything for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But the… but I think the output far outweighs what that cost is.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Again.
Dorothy: You could use…
Jeremiah Krakowski: ChatGPT Pro as well.
Jeremiah Krakowski: One thing you could get… kind of technical.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is you can get… NVIDIA is offering as part of their…
Jeremiah Krakowski: NIM program, you can get access to Kimmy K2.5, For free, to deploy…
Jeremiah Krakowski: for AI agents, for free from NVIDIA.com.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's one thing you can do. You can also get…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Some cheaper algorithms, let's say you use Open Router.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you can get an API key from Open Router, for, like, GLM5, Or…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, GLM5 is a really good one, Minimax 2.5…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Those are almost as good as Clawed, and they're a lot cheaper, see? So it's 30 cents for every million tokens.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a dollar for every million output, whereas Claude Opus 4.6 is $5.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Versus $25 every million output tokens. So you're looking at the difference of it's 25 times more expensive to use Claude.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Than to, say, use an,
Jeremiah Krakowski: an LLM like Minimax right here. However, Minimax and GLM5 are not as good at doing all the work, so that's the trade-off.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for those different types of things. And that's where it gets really technical.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's the side where, again, as I've been telling people, if you want me to help you set them up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I can help you do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If anybody who's, like, here wants me to help you set up
Jeremiah Krakowski: Your agents and things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just write me in Instagram, privately.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then we can work on that together, separately.
Jeremiah Krakowski: as kind of a separate project, until I get my… My thing launched.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I'll walk you through, kind of, the process of what you need for doing that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And the best way to do it. Now, again, I think that if you set it up with, like, GLM5 or Minimax, you will save quite a bit on tokens.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that is definitely a great way, as you're getting started with these agents, Is using those…
Jeremiah Krakowski: To start for building what you're doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I think Minimax 2.5 is really good at… with open claw, so…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And like I said, it's like 25 times cheaper.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so… Where were we? Okay, so what is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: an agent. An agent is basically…
Jeremiah Krakowski: A chatbot gives you ideas and information, an agent… Does work for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So instead of, okay, give me an idea for a landing page, now give me an idea for a graphic, now give me an idea for all that, the agent will literally come up with all of those ideas on its own by saying, build me a funnel for this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just the same way that you would hire a virtual assistant.
Jeremiah Krakowski: at a fraction of the cost of a virtual assistant. Because one Claude Max account for $200 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now, I'm running 14 AI agents right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have… 4 Claude Max accounts I'm running.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's $800 a month that I'm spending. It's costing me about $60 a month in Cloud Max tokens per agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's about $2 a day in Cloud Max usage.
Jeremiah Krakowski: per agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it's about $30 a day.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it… so that… but that's using Claude. Now, if I used Mini Max.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for 14 agents, that might only be…
Jeremiah Krakowski: A dollar or two a day.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That same amount of usage might only cost me $60.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If that makes sense.
Jeremiah Krakowski: but the quality… when I say quality of the output.
Jeremiah Krakowski: when you're using some of these other tools, it can be… it can be less accurate. It can be more frustrating.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It can be… like… less likely to produce the high-quality results that I'm looking for. So I'm…
Jeremiah Krakowski: More likely to spend $800 a month to get the quality output, then only $100 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because that extra $700 is the difference between me deploying things quickly that I know are high quality in my business or not.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So again, one Claude Max account, you could probably run 3 to 4 agents on.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I'm talking, like, you could run them, like, 24-7.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm using mine 24-7. If you're not using them 24-7, you could probably run, like, 4 to 7 agents on one CloudMax account.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So… which is pretty cool. For most of you, you're probably only gonna need, like, 2 or 3 agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Why would you need more than one agent? Because it's nice to have them be, like, a specialist. Like, I'll have one agent that writes… I have one agent that just writes emails.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For my mom and I.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, that's all it does.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have another agent that is, like, a researcher agent. That's all she does. She just gets better and better at researching.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have another agent that's, like, a virtual assistant. I have one that's, like, a coding agent. He makes software. I have one that's kind of an overall big picture agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so each of these different agents are specialists in different roles.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's how that works.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: All that to say, like, this can get very overwhelming fast.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's why, again.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I want to be able to help you guys be able to get these up and running. Again, if you write me on Instagram, you're gonna have to go take some time.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Go on my… all of you know how to find me on Instagram. Anybody who's watching this training.
Jeremiah Krakowski: knows how to find me on Instagram.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And…
Jeremiah Krakowski: So if you want help, like, setting… like, I just set up my mom's, Mac Mini at home.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so if you want to know, okay, how do we provision the right server for you? Do we want it at your house? Do we want it…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Do you want to use a Mac Mini? Do you want to use one of these, like, Windows computers you can buy? Maybe a Raspberry Pi? Do you want to use a server? I can help you get that set up, and then get everything set up for security correctly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because that's one of the biggest things, making sure that your security is set up correctly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that, you know, you're not… you're not giving all your personal information to these agents, and then it gets hacked, and then…
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, that'd be terrible. I'm confident that my agents could not get hacked.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I tried hacking into one of my agents the other day from my phone and couldn't do it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it was good. It was good that I had to take, like, 3… 3 extra steps to get access to my agents. It was not…
Jeremiah Krakowski: It was not easy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To hack into.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But getting all that set up correctly and the right way, that takes time, and that's where I want to help people get that set up. Again.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna be offering that as a full service to people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But for those of you that are, like, on these calls, you're watching, you're watching the recordings.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you send me a message on my Instagram, I can… I can help you with that. Okay, that's the… that's the end of that, all right? Like, I'm here as a resource, available to you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To be able to help you get those set up. And I'll tell you, like, what that costs and everything over on Instagram. It's kind of… it's different for each setup, so… but I'll make sure that it's reasonable, and I'll make sure that it fits, especially give everybody kind of a discount who's in this program here, okay? I know Tiffany's probably itching to see what kind of competitor analysis we found.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's pull this up. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Top trends in your space? The 4-burner Theory.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Life has four burners.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Family, work, health, friends. You can only run 3 at max.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Went massively viral. What?
Tiffany Quinones: I said facts. I'm just agreeing with Jill. Thank you, Jill.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Went massively viral on the 15th, picked up by different news outlets.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is your content, she should be all over it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Foreburner Theory, Proves what you've been saying. You can't perform… outperform burnout.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The 42% rule for high performers. You researchers say high performers need 42% of their day, in recovery.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Science is backing that rest is a superpower.
Tiffany Quinones: So these are all content ideas that you can build on.
Tiffany Quinones: Somatic shaking goes mainstream. Nervous system regulation.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Competitors, Mel Robbins. Mel is mainstream, Tiffany is specific to the leader dying inside. Brene Brown, Nicole La Pera.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So these are all… and these are all great, where she wins, foster care, origin story, nobody else has that.
Tiffany Quinones: voice-led activation.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Faith forward without being churchy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Raw authenticity.
Jeremiah Krakowski: 10 content ideas, the 4-burner Theory.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Scientists say 10 hours of recovery are needed, unbecoming the world that ended my burnout.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Gen Z figured it out, here's why it took me 30 years. Gen Z is officially rejecting hustle culture. Major article on Gen Z, watching influencers glamorize 4AM wakeups, then witnessing the burnout confessions.
Tiffany Quinones: You can only… which, by the way, you can only do a 4am wake up unless you're going to bed at, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: 9 to 11 p.m, you can't just stay, you know, sample 9.
Tiffany Quinones: Right.
Tiffany Quinones: Truth.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Boundaries may… let's see, Boundaries made the… oh, made the New York… yeah. New York Times feature, five books on setting better boundaries. New York Times just normalized boundary setting as mainstream.
Jeremiah Krakowski: See?
Tiffany Quinones: Yes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: time says it's trending, I've been screaming this from my car. I have been screaming it from my car. So those are some ideas, like, you know, I can send you those over.
Tiffany Quinones: Oh, please do, and then last week, you had mentioned you were gonna send me, and I posted it in the group.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just remind me, what to send over?
Tiffany Quinones: Yeah, last week, you had Joe create for me, it was like a… you put together a book, I think you did it for Dorothy, it was like a PDF type of a… it almost resembled Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Tiffany Quinones: You helped Dorothy create outcomes on what she's doing, so it's not just about yoga, and then you had Jill create for her something where she could,
Tiffany Quinones: take things to repurpose content. You did the same thing for me about repurposing my, podcast. I already started implementing using the testimonials, so I just went into ChatGPT
Tiffany Quinones: no, perplexity, and had it, create for me content to repurpose the testimonials in different ways. So I already started…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I just sent you the PDF.
Tiffany Quinones: Oh, thank you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is one of the reasons why I love using Slack with my agents, because it saves everything.
Dorothy: Yeah, that was really brilliant. Thanks, Jeremiah, what you did last week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So let me, let me send you yours, let me send you yours too, Dorothy.
Dorothy: Cheers.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And what they're talking about is that I had my agents create, like, a whole just leveraged business plan.
Jeremiah Krakowski: On… based on their businesses.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Of what to do, how to get it all going, and all that, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, but again, all this stuff…
Jeremiah Krakowski: like I said, can seem overwhelming. The two easiest
Jeremiah Krakowski: ways to get started with agents is lovable. Lovable is literally…
Jeremiah Krakowski: a clawed website building and app building agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That anybody can use.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it can do a lot more than just, like, what you guys, I think, think that Lovable can do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Lovable is essentially Claude… Code?
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's Claude Opus 4.6, built on their, interface.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But that's… but Lovable has basically built their whole business on creating an interface around Claude.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That creates websites and apps for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And there's also the plan mode inside of here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: you can do… there's the design mode, there's the… you have different connectors, MPC servers…
Jeremiah Krakowski: you can go into a project in Lovable, and you can just chat with it, too. Inside of Lovable, right here where it says Plan.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I can click plan mode, I can also click on… Let's see, that's visual edits…
Jeremiah Krakowski: So yeah, if I just go into, like, plan mode, I can just chat with it right there, which is awesome.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you can just talk with the agent about what you're wanting it to build, and the ideas that you have, and things like that. Have it come up with sales copy, have it come up with all those different things for you, right inside of Levable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, so, like, that's… that's one of the things, and then Manus…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Manis.im is, again, it's another agent platform, Meta owns them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's probably one of the easiest ways to get up and running with different agent workflows, because each
Jeremiah Krakowski: Sort of task that you give it turns into some kind of a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: An agent workflow that it can do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then you can set up… you can use the little agents function here, which is similar to what we did with OpenClaw.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I would have you kind of upgrade to having me set you up an open claw server, once you've kind of used these two… those two tools.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Once you've used Lovable, once you've used Manis a little bit.
Jeremiah Krakowski: you'll get an idea for what agents can do for you. Again, if a person can do it, an agent can.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And what I like is I will have my agents build me a tool if it doesn't know how to do something.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So one of the biggest things that I tell the agents to do is, it's like, oh, I can't do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Great.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Go learn how to.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because anything that an agent tells me it can't do, it can learn how to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then it will go to work, and I'll tell it, and don't stop until you figure it out.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it will figure out exactly how to do what I need it to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I've not found anywhere where it's not been able to figure out how to do something, even if it said it didn't know how to.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, so with this, what I want is… I want us to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: move beyond just… and we're gonna go a little bit longer here, because we've kind of been answering questions, and I've been teaching back and forth a little bit here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: you know, any of the questions that kind of come up for you guys while I've been talking about this, let's post some of them in the chat. Just anything. I want this to kind of be like a flow, like, let's get into kind of like a flow state of just all of our questions that we have. Let's get them all out on the table.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's kind of talk about this, because what I want to do is I want you guys to leave here today.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is, again, this is gonna be a teaching… coaching Q&A hybrid around Getting your stuff going.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Getting stuff off the ground, launching a campaign. I want you to get your… I want you to get…
Jeremiah Krakowski: An actual campaign launched, That's marketing your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's getting you clients, that you have an agent that built… that's built for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, like, what's the biggest thing that stops us from doing that?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is it having everything set up?
Jeremiah Krakowski: in the right order? Is it all those things? By the way, I've learned with agents, I don't need everything to be set up in the right order.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I can have it go out of order and just create what I need in the moment.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that gives us a lot of freedom to come up with ideas for what we're doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay But, like, what we have is… So the first thing is, Create a lovable account, Use that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Get a landing page made. Start playing around with maybe rebuilding a website with it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You don't need to rebuild your whole website, too. You could just build, like, an offer page.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The same way that people use ClickFunnels for, I would use Lovable for. I wouldn't even use ClickFunnels.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would just use Levable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, like, the prompt is what builds the page that you have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You kind of feed into it different ideas of what you do. Now, here's the cool thing about using Lovable, is you can change it on the fly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you don't like what it produced, you can tell it, I don't like that, make it more like this, make it more like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It needs to be more on this topic, it needs to be more on that topic.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then here's the beautiful part about it with Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can connect anything in Lovable, if you have a Stripe account, you can just connect Stripe to your Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you just tell Lovable, I have a Stripe account.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I want people to be able to spend money with me, Through this page.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it will literally just walk you through the steps of giving it what it needs from Stripe to be able to do that. So, like, in Stripe, you need to grab what's called a webhook, and then there's, like, an API key inside of Stripe that it needs.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Honestly, I don't think you necessarily need Stand Store. I think you could probably just have Levable build you what StandStore has.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And run all of it through there, easily.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then from there, You can go live with something that way.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You need some… you need to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Have somewhere to put people's, emails.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, these are the infrastructures right here that you can use. You can either use something like ConvertKit…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Mailerlite, Systemi I.O,
Jeremiah Krakowski: whatever you're comfortable with, then all you gotta do is you just tell Levable, hey, I want you to help me create an automation to where when somebody purchases this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: they automatically get added into my ConvertKit account, my Systeme I.O, my… MailerLite account.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, so those are kind of, like, the three connectors.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That you pretty much need, for funnel staff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is you need some kind of a… Email… Software?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm not talking about Gmail, I'm talking about, like, you need to have, like, a MailChimp. I don't like MailChimp anymore that much, it's so expensive.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Mailerlite.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Systemi.io, ConvertKit, these all have great free tiers, and are… I think MailerLite's one of the best as far as pricing goes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because as you grow, they're not gonna charge you more.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know, I can have… I can send out 5 emails a day in MailerLite, and have…
Jeremiah Krakowski: 5,000 subscribers and still not pay more than 60 bucks a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: MailChimp would charge me… $1,000 for that, a month, that Meller Lite's only charging $50 for.
Jeremiah Krakowski: No, no, I will say that's one thing, like, I'm gonna have my agents look into, like, building a mail software, but honestly, I think
Jeremiah Krakowski: it might not even be worth it. I have to look at, like, what's the backend servers behind mail software or something like that, but…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Not worried about that right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: it's so cheap, it's like, it's worth it to just use MillerLite.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, again, you have your agent inside of Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: or inside of Manus, again, Manus can go log into your MailerLite account and go grab everything that you need. Manus can log into Lovable. You could literally… this is how I would see, for most of you, like, using agents, you could use Lovable and Manus together and tell Manus to log into Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And connect these things together for you, even if you find it too technical.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Very easy to do. And then if you have an open claw agent, if you have…
Jeremiah Krakowski: me sets you up a server, or you get one of these open claw agents set up, I can absolutely, absolutely do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Manus is gonna be better on a computer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But it works tremendously well on a phone. The thing with it, doing it on a computer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is you can actually give it… there's a plugin for your Chrome web browser, where Manus can actually take control of your browser and do stuff inside the browser.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which is really cool. So it can literally, like, log into your Lovable account. It can log into that from Manus. And that's why Manus is so powerful.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For what they offered.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, the phone version is… is… you can't do that with… Okay, then, from there…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You have a landing page?
Jeremiah Krakowski: You have it connected to an email software, you have it connected to Stripe, right?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So we have our email software, we have Stripe.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We have… lovable, We're gonna connect it to those things, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Then what we need is we need some kind of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Advertisement.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you need something that's an ad for your social media that is a… like an ad image, an ad video that you can make. You can have AI, these tools, generate you these different ad tools.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, tonight, you can get lovable set up with Stripe, You could…
Jeremiah Krakowski: draft up in ChatGPT or Gemini or Claude some ideas for emails that'll go in the automation. You can load the email automation into an email software. You can make some ad graphics.
Jeremiah Krakowski: right inside of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: right inside, Manus is pretty good at this, you can make them inside of ChatGPT or Gemini.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Honestly, you could probably use Manus for most of this stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you have Manus, you could probably cancel your ChatGBT or Gemini account and save some money there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For most people, like, your agents can kind of take
Jeremiah Krakowski: take over what you're doing with ChatGPT.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You set up an ad in the ads manager, you make a post on your social media about the offer that you just built.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And, like, that whole process right there… To launch a $5 mini-class.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To launch a… a free ebook of some kind.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To launch a free webinar.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to launch…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And by the way, I don't think people are as likely to go through, like, 5-day or 7-day challenges as much as they were before.
Jeremiah Krakowski: unless they're deep inside your ecosystem, I think people want to watch through, like, a 30-minute video, or they want to read, like, a bullet point
Jeremiah Krakowski: article, or e-book, That's generated. About…
Jeremiah Krakowski: What to do and about your framework.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To make decisions to work with you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so you could get this all set up by having Lovable, pretty much…
Jeremiah Krakowski: connect everything, and then if lovable can't, you can have Manus help you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: By logging into these things, To get them all set up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, like, what would be… the factor… The underlying factor
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's kind of preventing us from From doing that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Mary says, I'll look into Lovable, I'm in the midst of rebranding, don't know what direction to go. Start with a podcast.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Mary, help me understand what's going on?
Mary Chalhoub: I guess, okay, so I got kind of distracted, I got involved the last several months.
Mary Chalhoub: launching this school with a few other people, and it took all my time, and then I lost track of my own stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I feel… That happens. Yeah.
Mary Chalhoub: So I feel like I'm kind of starting all over again.
Mary Chalhoub: And trying to find where to start, where to launch. I want a fresh… I don't know, I feel…
Mary Chalhoub: I need a fresh start.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, podcasts is a great way to kind of get your thoughts out there.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I know Tiffany really had a great, some great traction by getting her podcast launched, and then that's led into everything else that she's been doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because each week, or a couple times a week, she's able to just record it in her car, or do something to get her ideas out there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… She doesn't need to, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Wait until she has a course, or wait until she has a lesson or a masterclass.
Mary Chalhoub: Huh.
Jeremiah Krakowski: or writes her next book, or things like that. That's one of the reasons why I actually launched my podcast the way that I did, and it always helped me stay on track with just keeping my ideas fresh that I'm sharing with people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Before I had a coaching program.
Mary Chalhoub: Right.
Mary Chalhoub: I guess my thing is, like, I can go in…
Mary Chalhoub: like, there are 10 different directions I can go, and I keep, like…
Mary Chalhoub: going back and forth, I'm like, well, should I…
Mary Chalhoub: focus on this, or this, or this, or that, or… and I kind of… I feel like I have to hone in my…
Mary Chalhoub: Target audience, and… who I'm speaking to…
Mary Chalhoub: before I get started, but there are several…
Mary Chalhoub: areas I can speak into, and I… and so now I'm just in that Stuck place, you know?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think the… I think the biggest thing is you're probably looking for certainty.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: About… what's gonna work.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that… Is ne… that's not gonna happen until we…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Actually start putting stuff out there.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay. Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's one of the biggest things, is like, oftentimes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that's where we get stuck, because I'm not sure which direction to go in.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the biggest thing I would just tell you is, like, pray.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And see which one feels right.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Mary Chalhoub: You know? Like, which one of the directions that you want to go feels right?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which one really lights you up the most?
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Start there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… which one… Are people constantly asking you for help with?
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then how do you kind of merge the one that lights you up and the one that people constantly ask you for help with?
Mary Chalhoub: Together.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so they might be the same, they might be different.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But that's the direction, because if people are asking for help with it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and it lights you up, which, by the way, like, the AI agent stuff for me is literally the direct convergence of those two things. So that's why I've been, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: so excited to lean into this, because it's… it combines everything that I've been passionate about, that I know is going to help people get results.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so… from here, for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You will not have the certainty
Jeremiah Krakowski: of, is this the direction, necessarily, that I want to go? Let's… but let's… let's take a look at this here, because we can kind of, like I did with Tiffany, I… we did, like, a whole research thing. So what are the directions that you want to go in? Let's kind of research some of these with one of my… my research agents and see what she comes up with.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because we might be able to actually give you some clarity right now. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because the difference is that my agent is trained on all my content, and it understands the marketplace, and it understands how to build these types of businesses. So give me the different kind of directions that you're thinking of.
Mary Chalhoub: Well, when you say, what do people ask you a lot, of questions on, I get a lot of people who…
Mary Chalhoub: Ask me about book writing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Mary Chalhoub: A lot of questions on that. Yeah.
Mary Chalhoub: And strangely, it's the area I have the most resistance in, because I have to…
Mary Chalhoub: Believe it or not, it just doesn't come…
Mary Chalhoub: naturally, like, I just feel like I have to… it takes everything in me to sit down and start writing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Mary Chalhoub: But… I did have, you know, pretty good success with my first book, And…
Mary Chalhoub: I don't know why. I… that wasn't enough to, like.
Mary Chalhoub: I don't know, I just always feel like there's a little bit of a resistance there, but I get a lot of people asking me about book writing.
Mary Chalhoub: The other area is spiritual equipping.
Mary Chalhoub: Because I've… I've been ordained in a few.
Mary Chalhoub: different ministries, and sorry, I'm on a treadmill.
Jeremiah Krakowski: No, you're good.
Mary Chalhoub: Let me stop quickly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think for you, sometimes you wonder if what you're… if what you're doing is good enough.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah, and then I kind of… There are things that…
Mary Chalhoub: I see going on, and I'm just like… it just kind of turns me off to that…
Mary Chalhoub: I just have… conflicting thoughts, because… of…
Mary Chalhoub: things that I see going on around me, and…
Mary Chalhoub: And I'm like, do I really want to do this? Like, but yet I'm passionate about it. It's really weird. Like, it's my mind and my heart kind of…
Mary Chalhoub: Fighting.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, a lot of it, it's your nervous system, and it's your…
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's your beliefs that you have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's your… Goals, dreams, aspirations, it's your faith.
Mary Chalhoub: All kind of colliding together with the reality of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: The fact that you're human, And you feel things very deeply.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you see things that you know are not right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you want to do better.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's all good stuff.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What I would say is this, is that
Jeremiah Krakowski: Cause I know there's a lot… there's been a… there's been a lot of stuff that's…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Happened over the last couple of weeks in the… prophetic space.
Mary Chalhoub: Well, months, actually, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Months, even the past couple years.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Mike?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I had a conversation, you know who Will Ford is?
Mary Chalhoub: Mmm, no, I don't.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay. Will Ford is, he wrote a… book with, Cindy Jacobs and Lou Engel.
Mary Chalhoub: Oh, God.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know who they are, I'm sure.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's kind of in that… that realm. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I had a conversation with him, he said that what's happening right now, like, in that whole space is there's just a purifying.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that's happening, and the people that are pure with the Lord.
Jeremiah Krakowski: He's gonna be elevated.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know, and so I believe that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I, I, I really believe that, and I, I'm still connected with
Jeremiah Krakowski: different leaders in the… in that space and stuff like that. I…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I just… I find that there's… that's a lot of… there's a lot of truth to that. So, like, that's the thing to know, is like, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Examine your heart, see if there's anywhere…
Jeremiah Krakowski: where you need to ask God to… Clean those areas out.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then have Faith that… and walk in…
Jeremiah Krakowski: The fact that actually doors are opening to you that might not have been previously open because so many things are falling by the wayside.
Mary Chalhoub: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: space right now, to now it creates opportunity for you to step in as a pure voice.
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, like, that's just my… that's just my kind of, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: prophetic exhortation to you on that. Yeah. On that, I would say…
Jeremiah Krakowski: That then, it's like, when we make it practical for…
Jeremiah Krakowski: What directions to go in your…
Jeremiah Krakowski: In what you're doing in ministry and business?
Jeremiah Krakowski: The areas where we have the most resistance, I think.
Jeremiah Krakowski: it's good to lean into those, and to say… because resistance doesn't necessarily mean that it's a bad thing. Oftentimes, resistance comes when it is the right thing to do.
Mary Chalhoub: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If the resistance is, like, not the door closing, because it's just, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now, at the same time, what you'll find is that the resistance often comes because we're…
Jeremiah Krakowski: We're using the wrong key for the right door.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is what it is.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So the resistance comes because we're trying to use an old method.
Mary Chalhoub: I see.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To get through a door that we're meant to walk through.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's an open door, but we need the right access.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then as soon as you have the right access, the right tools, the right ways to walk through them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It becomes very easy. It becomes very simple. It's not… that striving.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right. To be able to step into those areas, okay? So that… that's the… that's the one side of it that I would say for you, and then the other side is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You're… you gotta get comfortable making uncomfortable decisions.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That you're… that you have uncertainty about.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And, and… When it comes to business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: there's going to be uncertain things. Now, that's where having these different kind of research
Jeremiah Krakowski: tools, I just, like, now that I've been able to set up these different AI agents and stuff like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The ability to research and have more clarity in my business?
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's so much more powerful
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because of that. So what… when you say you have multiple directions that you could go in, like, just list off real quickly what are some of those directions?
Mary Chalhoub: Well, some of the directions are, like, the prophetic, Or spiritual gifts, like…
Mary Chalhoub: equipping and training. Some of it is… More heart healing, self-image.
Mary Chalhoub: Then sometimes I think, am I speaking to women? Am I speaking to women and men?
Mary Chalhoub: Should I just do practical things like book writing?
Mary Chalhoub: Like, a book writing course, or a club, or,
Mary Chalhoub: Other areas are… that I'm very passionate about are worship and, prophetic art.
Mary Chalhoub: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I think, I think, like, what you just mentioned.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would say, like.
Mary Chalhoub: The worship and prophetic art can kind of be…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Sort of like the, like the, like the cherry on top, the frosting on top of everything else?
Mary Chalhoub: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know? But implement it, and I think you could actually implement all of these things together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think that healing the heart.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Self-image.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think definitely you have a message… you're… I think you have a message.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That women resonate with.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… I think men and women can resonate with it, but I think that women probably.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Would benefit more.
Mary Chalhoub: Like, for example, I have… I did build a team.
Mary Chalhoub: Like, I have an online team, we… like, an intersession team, we pray together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Mary Chalhoub: and stuff, and I was quite… I mean, it's really split…
Mary Chalhoub: Men and women. It's half men.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Very cool.
Mary Chalhoub: women, so I…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I was curious about that. I know you mentioned that before, as if it stayed that way.
Mary Chalhoub: Yes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That kind of seems like you really do attract sort of a split half and half.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think that would be good. I find… I find this interesting for me, I probably have more women that I activate.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to their success than I do, necessarily, even men.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I… and I just… it's always been that way, because I've always worked with strong, powerful women business leaders.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I've had to learn how to kind of navigate
Jeremiah Krakowski: how do you… how do I have a conversation with a woman business owner versus a, you know, a male business owner?
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's just… it's just different.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… and so I think that, like, finding, again, who are you attracting, who is… who is getting the most results from what you do, that's kind of the
Jeremiah Krakowski: That you want to focus in on?
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: as far as that side of it, is, again, who gets the most results? Who… who do you see as, like, the, like… and it could just be, like, two people, even. Three people?
Jeremiah Krakowski: that they've…
Jeremiah Krakowski: followed everything that you've done, and they've seen exponential growth in their life. Those are the people that you really kind of want to build what you're doing in your next season off of, what they.
Mary Chalhoub: There's a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: story was, and then how it connects to your story, and how it connects to this whole bigger picture of things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So now what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna take what we just talked about, and I'm gonna bring this into…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And this'll take a few… it might take, like, 5-10 minutes to process this.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the agent, but I'm gonna take… I'm gonna take what we just talked about.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna pull this in here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see… Oh no, it's frozen.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Scroll down… The note-taker, are you still there?
Mary Chalhoub: Me?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Mary Chalhoub: Yes, I'm here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, great. Let me see… transcript… Notetaker… okay, there we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let me go… Alright, first…
Jeremiah Krakowski: There we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, sorry, I'm trying to… I'm trying to get this transcript down here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I have the transcript of what we just talked about. Let's do this right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, now I'm.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay, that was…
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is gonna help us get some, like… Clarity on all this.
Mary Chalhoub: Huh.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, Jill… Take the following transcript from a conversation I had with Mary…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can look her up online and find what she's… Worked on.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Take what we talked about, and help her gain some clarity on what direction to go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… Where to start?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like… Okay. Simply because I know that it's built in with all my frameworks and all that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see, use all the frameworks and information…
Jeremiah Krakowski: that you have about the business models that I… teach people… We've come up with this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's what I'm gonna… I'm gonna send it, and then we're gonna… we're gonna come up with this, and turn this into a beautiful PDF.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That I can share with her. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So we're gonna kind of come back to that once that is…
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: created.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just take a look at that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see, Dorothy says, with my intro, $5 yoga course.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where would you store the videos? I mean, you could store them on Vimeo.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could store them as private YouTube videos.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could store them in Thinkific, you could store them in a school community.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could store them… on a Google Drive link?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I use Google Drive frequently, for different things, just to give people access to stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: After they pay for it, you just get the link and you send it to them?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, like, those are all really easy ways to do that, or you could, you know, set up something in, like, a school community, or a Teachable account, or in Vimeo somewhere. Vimeo has these things called, like, password-protected playlists. You could send the playlist to somebody.
Dorothy: Yeah, because I've got a school account for my yoga membership, but my administrator was saying that, like, if I was doing a separate course, that they would still have to log in to my membership.
Dorothy: if they still have to get the membership, but I wasn't sure if that was actually the case.
Dorothy: whether you can have separate things, because I know it's really easy with Thinkific, isn't it? You can have different bundles that people are…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think in school, I think you can, you can have different courses be, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Different access inside the school community.
Dorothy: Oh, okay, yeah.
Dorothy: Okay, oh, that's good to know, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If they're a part of your membership, I would just give them the $5 course. $5 course is not necessarily for people that are in the membership, so I would just give people the course.
Dorothy: Yeah. And they have to pay to join the membership.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For the $5 course, but again, you could also just give them the videos through a link somewhere, as well.
Dorothy: Great.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Dorothy: So it could be a separate Google Drive, so you can have, like, multiple Google Drives.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right.
Dorothy: If you… Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I mean, I wanna do something else here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Wanna make a really nice… Graphic here for you guys.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna go into… let's see… Fuse Nano Banana.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To make a nice outline graphic for my clients of the process.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna make you guys a graphic I'm gonna post to the group here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Based on what we've talked about here today, Just a nice outline.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright, it's building the comprehensive clarity document for Mary.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think the biggest thing that we gotta get to a place of is where We don't let… anything.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I just… I mean anything.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Slow us down.
Jeremiah Krakowski: from iterating.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And getting our offers out there, without burning ourselves out, without needing to sit in front of a computer for 25 million hours.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you start to utilize these new tools that exist.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To reach people with your offer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to reach people with… with what you're… with what you're offering. So again, like, let's go big picture here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I just want to kind of map this out here. So that's kind of like the tech side of setting it up, right?
Jeremiah Krakowski: None of that changes What we've been talking about for…
Jeremiah Krakowski: 3, 4 years now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For 3-4 years now, I've been showing you this process.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Number 1.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You find the right people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: you use AI to figure out who they are. Now, with an agent, this whole step right here, the find.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Write sales copy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Build Funnel.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: promote…
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's all now in one step with an AI agent. So what we were able to… what we… like, remember? You find the people, you write the copy, you figure out, like, who that niche is, you figure out your niche.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You find your niche.
Jeremiah Krakowski: write the copy, you build the funnel, you start promoting it. That can all be done in, like, one step now with agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay? So this is agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so agents, you can pretty much have the agents do, like, everything.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For those steps.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then, number 5… Is you sell, And then you… Analyze.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Analysis. Agents can do the whole thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The selling?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is agent assisted?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So one of the main things the agents can't necessarily…
Jeremiah Krakowski: The agents can…
Jeremiah Krakowski: They can't necessarily, like, sell for you, they, like, you have to be the one that talks and sells.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You have to be the one that communicates, you have to be the one that coaches with people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so with that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The agent, though, can assist you in, what's your script for your webinar?
Jeremiah Krakowski: What's your sales script when you are communicating with Client on the phone.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can have the agent automate writing people in the direct messages, in DMs. I showed you guys, like, a month ago, in Manus doing that. Now with OpenClaw, you can have it just log into your Instagram and start sending DMs to people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To message them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, like, almost, like, the entire process that I used to have to teach you manually to do, the agents can do. Finding your niche, you figure out that with the AI,
Jeremiah Krakowski: we did that with AI all the time, originally.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Writing the copy, building the funnel, launching the ads, creating the ads… Agents can do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Selling, you can use agents to assist you with selling, and then analyzing the whole process, and reiterating.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The agent can do all that as well.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So just kind of keep that in mind. Alright, here we go, here's Mary's… PDF right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Correction and Clarity Blueprint.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Personalized Roadmap, prepared for Mary Shaleb, author of Destined to Shine, Securing Your True Identity.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Published author…
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is you, right?
Mary Chalhoub: Where I don't see me… yeah, that's me, and…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, Mary, you don't have a direction problem, you have a decision problem, masked as a clarity problem.
Mary Chalhoub: Oh, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the conversation. There are 10 different directions I can go, I keep going back and forth.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's not 10 options, that's 1 calling with 10 expressions.
Mary Chalhoub: Hmm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Everything you listed, book writing, spiritual equipping, heart healing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They orbit around the same center, helping people secure their true identity so they can shine.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Literally the title of your book.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the convergence of where it all comes together, using Jeremiah's framework, what lights you up, what do people consistently ask you about?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Identity Reclamation through faith.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The book writing is proof that you've walked the path, spiritual equipping is the how, heart healing is the self-image, is the transformation, worship and art is the atmosphere shifting.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So this is your unique positioning.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Start a podcast this week, right there.
Mary Chalhoub: You use Podbean to do that.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: First 10 episodes, I lost myself helping everybody else.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Why self-doubt is a spiritual issue.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Not just a mindset problem. What breast cancer taught me about identity.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The performing trap, when your ministry becomes your mask.
Mary Chalhoub: Man, it even knew I had breast cancer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It found… it found the info about you, yeah. What's?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, I didn't know that, but it did.
Mary Chalhoub: Mmm, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yup.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And if you want to use that or not, you can. I think it does have… there's a… I think there's definitely a lot of power in that part of the story.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Writing the book that healed me while your story matters. Build a $5 entry product, $5 identity assessment, $5 Shine Workshop.
Jeremiah Krakowski: group coaching.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then… so this could be, like, $4.97 for 3 months, $197 a month, start with 10 to 20 people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You have something 90% of them don't, a published book.
Jeremiah Krakowski: how to use it. Podcast episodes, $5 product, group coaching.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The book itself can all be kind of used to guide through that. Use your old book to guide people to whatever the next thing that you're doing is.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So again, hold on.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What's up?
Mary Chalhoub: My dog just ran out. I didn't realize. Okay, I'm listening.
Mary Chalhoub: I'm just…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You're good.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, so… yeah, so podcast, entry level.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You got the book, you got a low-ticket kind of offer here. Then you can start offering, kind of, like, a group coaching.
Mary Chalhoub: And a VIP mentoring for $1,500 to $3,000.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you don't have to teach how to write a book, that's the old key, technical, draining, yeah.
Mary Chalhoub: Huh.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It teaches people how to find their voice through writing.
Mary Chalhoub: That's good.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's the identity work.
Mary Chalhoub: Huh.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And this is what I love, because, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It probably… I probably would have taken me a couple days to kind of get to this right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the AI agent, because it's trained on what I've done, and it was able to look up what you do, and all that, and our conversation, and it was able to pull all that together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to really realize, like, that's what you need to do. You're helping people find their voice through writing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Overcoming their fear that their story matters, finding their voice. Writing as an act of healing, using writing as a healing part of their journey.
Mary Chalhoub: Wow, that's good. The healed rider type of a thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Turning their testimony into a tool to help others.
Jeremiah Krakowski: write your shine, the spirit-led book writing experience, could be a whole thing right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yup.
Mary Chalhoub: So… Can I get a copy of that?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay, awesome.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so I… I think, like, just right there, that's where…
Mary Chalhoub: Huh.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now, the value is, like, if you got that all set up with your own agent, then you could kind of build upon that, and have it then start building out all the different resources for you.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: agent could go in and literally create the podcast for you. Go in and do all that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's what's powerful now, is these… is these agents…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Anything that, like, you would do technically, or…
Jeremiah Krakowski: On a computer, you could have… The… the system do it.
Mary Chalhoub: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which is just so… so cool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, yeah, let me send you that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that file.
Mary Chalhoub: Great, thank you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Adele, you still here?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is Adele still here?
Adele Best: Yeah, I just couldn't get the mute button off. I'm still here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Take a look at this.
Adele Best: Already hit our launch… wow, did it create this PDF? That's amazing. Build your page, connect Stripe. Love it, get your automated. It's funny, because in my mind's eye, that's what I was aware that I had to do that. Create your offer, yep.
Adele Best: mini class.
Adele Best: Graphics and copy in seconds go live and sell.
Adele Best: I love it. It's brilliant.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So this is now kind of the process of getting your offer out there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is… and it's agents all the way.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Adele Best: I love it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For doing this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Adele Best: So, if we create an ads account and the email automation, obviously create an offer somewhere, and then tell it to go and create the ads.
Adele Best: It should be able to do that, and we can do that in Manus, yeah?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, you can do it Manus. Like, using Manus and lovable together would probably be great.
Adele Best: That might be a sort of a really easy next step for us, if we don't want to go all the way to an agent, like, this might be a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah. Well, Manus does have that tab you can play with the agent tab, too.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And see, kind of, how it works.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Inside of me.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, I trust Manis a lot, because Meta… owns them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: As far as from a safety and security and kind of being able to set everything up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right? And Manus is a really… it's a mature platform.
Jeremiah Krakowski: they were actually the first AI agent platform that existed.
Jeremiah Krakowski: was Manus. They launched almost a year and a half ago.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I still think, like, Manus is one of the best tools that's very easy for anybody to create an account with and start using agents with.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, but yeah, that's the… that's kind of the launch sprint right there.
Adele Best: Okay, I've screenshotted that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We're getting our offer launched. I'm gonna go put it in the group, too.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because this is… truly…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And, like, what we just went over right here, like, that's, like, I need to make some YouTube videos on that. I need to start talking about, like, this simple process of using agents to do those steps. Because now what we just did was we made it practical. We took it from, like, have an agent build your business to, like, okay, what do you actually have the agent do for you?
Adele Best: Yeah, so your, your quick start thing's changed a bit now. Your Quick Start training.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What's up?
Adele Best: You know the way you did your fast-track training for newcomers?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Adele Best: It's kind of like that now. It's just…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yes, that needs to be updated.
Adele Best: Yeah, that's 19th.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So… Definitely.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know, we all talk about resistance that we have. My biggest resistance has just been, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The past week with my wife's mom being in the hospital and all that, and… I was like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna get my AI Agents course started, and then this happens, and then…
Jeremiah Krakowski: So sometimes you just gotta give yourself grace to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Take another week to get something out there.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: How's everybody feel about all this?
Adele Best: I'm excited. It's good.
Jeremiah Krakowski: else that, like, it feels confusing, we're not sure about?
Adele Best: Like, so can we tell Manus, like, because I'd also like to create a podcast as a lead magnet, that they go onto the website, or wherever, and they.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yes, you could have Manis research, kind of, how to get the podcast up and do all the setup.
Adele Best: Yeah, so just give Manas my book, and say, create a podcast out of that that's gonna use sales psychology to reverse engineer them to my first offer ladder, like, that's gonna.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would have it give you, like, your first 10, kind of, podcast episode ideas with descriptions.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then kind of how to set… and then have it set up the technical side of the podcast?
Adele Best: And I can even just clone my voice in Eleven Labs and just get AI to make them for me.
Adele Best: If I really didn't want to do that.
Adele Best: I think that's an option. Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Definitely.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's awesome.
Dorothy: So would you say to put Podbean onto your website? Would that be something you'd do? Where would you have your podcasts?
Dorothy: Running.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you can either use Podbean, or, like, you can just create a self-hosted podcast
Jeremiah Krakowski: thing, like, I have my agents that they just created a podcast for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But, so when you have a podcast, you need to have the audio files somewhere.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's what Podbean does right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And they do so… this is, let's see, unlimited audio right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then what it'll… what it'll do is it'll actually… it'll submit it to all the different podcasts
Jeremiah Krakowski: platforms like Spotify and Apple and all those for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Amazon Music, Because the way that you actually get a podcast out there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is this little thing called an RSS feed.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And what a podcast RSS feed looks like is… Looks like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Should be able to find it.
Dorothy: So I'm thinking of branching out to do something a bit like, Headspace.
Dorothy: with, audio.
Dorothy: Relaxation.
Dorothy: As well as a podcast.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you're gonna do something like that, I would build it more as an app instead of lovable.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, you go to Lovable, I wanna, I want… To do something like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Headspace for relaxation, kind of a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Podcast, something with audios, like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Can you build this for me?
Dorothy: See?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it's like… it's like that easy is… has how you prompt, level.
Dorothy: GPT, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then what it's doing is it's exploring, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: All the different ways that you would build out That whole ecosystem.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's gonna build us out an example of this.
Dorothy: Right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: what I've been doing with my agents is I give them an idea like that, and then I say, okay, now let's go make a server.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's go build it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And let's create that software.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then it just builds me whatever I'm…
Dorothy: Wow. So that, that would actually be inside lovable.
Dorothy: So, it could be an app.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to build it in Lovable, but then you can publish it, anywhere.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you can add a custom domain, you can publish it online.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So would it be, guided meditation, ambient sounds, sleep stories, breathing exercises?
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which ones would it be?
Dorothy: Well, I think it would be, definitely…
Dorothy: guided meditations and deep relaxation. There'll be a lot of specific things, so I do a whole series
Dorothy: For people with ME and chronic fatigue.
Dorothy: then there'd be a series around meditation, mindfulness.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Will it be a series on what?
Dorothy: Meditation and mindfulness.
Jeremiah Krakowski: chronic fatigue.
Dorothy: Yeah, and and me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright, let's have it just kind of start from here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where do the audio files come from?
Dorothy: So it's deep breath work.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Upload your own… Calm and minimal, nature-inspired, dark immersive, or what tone?
Dorothy: Probably… calmer minimal, I'd say.
Dorothy: Definitely nature inspired.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They can create user accounts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is gonna be a really nice app.
Jeremiah Krakowski: How detailed should the profiles be? Just basic profile.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For a series like Chronic Fatigue or Mindfulness sessions to be sequential or freely accessible.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Remote open access, so they can jump to session to session.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Partial in order, or they can jump from session to session.
Dorothy: Oh, definitely… well, I'd say they can jump from session to session, but ideally they're doing them in order, but they might find that there's one that works for them the best, you know, and then they want to jump straight to that one.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Great.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and this is a whole new thing they've added into Lovable here, where it starts asking you more of these questions, because the idea is the agent is now coming up with, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The best way to kind of deliver your idea to you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is what it's doing.
Dorothy: That's pretty neat.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So this is kind of the plan.
Dorothy: Fantastic.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Create it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's gonna take a little bit to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's gotta write all the code.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So in the backend, see, it's writing all this code.
Dorothy: Amazing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: How it's gonna put it all together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So everything's all written in code, in Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There's our plan.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So now it's gonna start setting this up for you, and then I can…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I can actually send you this project and transfer ownership of it to you.
Dorothy: Wow. Amazing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So then… You can start using it yourself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And just to get to that point, we only used, three and a half credits.
Dorothy: Yep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: On my account. So, Lovable uses credits.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let me see, transfer ownership…
Dorothy: and then I could put it on something like Audible, Thomas.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What's your,
Jeremiah Krakowski: Oh, interesting.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's in the workspace…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let me give you an invite link right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I don't know if it's gonna go on Audible with this, but it'll.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could probably build it out to do something like that eventually.
Jeremiah Krakowski: once you put something into Audible, it,
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's not paid access, it's free.
Dorothy: Oh.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So just kind of keep that in mind, like.
Dorothy: Okay, so would it be better to have it on SoundCloud, then?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, unless you're… No, I mean, SoundCloud's pretty… pretty old and outdated.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I wouldn't use SoundCloud.
Dorothy: So, with something like Headspace, I know Passion.io is used a lot, isn't it?
Dorothy: People doing that kind of thing, you know.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yup.
Dorothy: Or, or, you know, just audio relaxation.
Dorothy: Because a lot of people with ME,
Dorothy: and chronic fatigue don't like looking at the screen. That's pretty standard, that, you know, if I'm teaching yoga, so I've got a number of students that
Dorothy: And that's why I teach in a particular way, and I describe as much as I can. But all the students that can't look at the screen.
Dorothy: You know, so I think there's a definite, huge market for it just being audible, you know, audio. And it's just where the best place is to put that, where you could charge a membership.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, yeah, so to charge your membership.
Dorothy: I would not…
Jeremiah Krakowski: at this stage, invest in Passion.io.
Dorothy: Yeah. You can build it all inside of Lovable.
Dorothy: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Passion.io is kind of before…
Jeremiah Krakowski: a lot of these AI tools, and they're just charging exponentially for
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, you can easily have something like Lovable build for you.
Dorothy: So I could have, like, a funnel with Facebook ads that would go to lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And all the audio would be there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yep.
Dorothy: Oh, that would be great, yeah. Because school is very specific, really, to, like, it's more, like, set out, like, an environment where you are watching videos, you are, sort of.
Dorothy: You know, it's different to, say, if somebody's, you know, on the hop and they're…
Dorothy: They just want to listen to something, they're on a train, and they want to listen to some relaxation.
Dorothy: You know, that kind of thing. So, has Lovable got a big storage? You could have, like, because
Dorothy: you know, I'm sort of talking about hundreds of potential audios.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let me see, they have their cloud platform right here that you can add storage buckets.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So right here, like, a new storage bucket.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's right there. Yes, you can add more storage into it that way.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you need more, it's like, let's see, disk…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Usage, that gives you 9 gigabytes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Do we need to increase it to, say, 200?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or, like, a hundred and a hundred and… if you're gonna have that many audios, yeah, I'd say, like, 160…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Increased disk size… 260 gigabytes… So that's gonna increase your disk size that much, 260 gigabytes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's being updated, we can upgrade your instance.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to… larger… Like, more visitors and stuff like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So right here, let's see, there's the login screen, here's the kind of… Homepage of it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Sign in the preview, then add. Okay, let's, sign up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, check your email.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have to go check my email to confirm it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I don't see an email.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Commit.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see, there's the backend…
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, what I would say to it right here…
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is now where you gotta go back and forth with it. Like, I… so I didn't get… I didn't receive the email when I signed up, so I didn't receive the sign-up email to sign in. There's also no opening landing page. So now that's where you gotta have to talk back and forth with the agent.
Dorothy: Yep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, okay, what's not working?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Instead of getting frustrated, we just… Take a look at.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What needs to be… Okay, auto-confirm is enabled.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Oh, there we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see, meditation, this is where the series would be there. Mindfulness, chronic fatigue, breathing…
Dorothy: Brilliant.
Jeremiah Krakowski: profile, this is where they can have, like, their streaks.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Favorites, they could find different series in here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They can see different access, those different things. So then…
Jeremiah Krakowski: How do I administrate this to upload content?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So now it has to build you, like, a whole admin workflow. So that's the thing, like, it kind of has to build out everything for you, if you can do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So… Now it's gonna build out a whole, like, page for you to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Log in and upload video… upload audios and stuff like that into here.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, that's the thing, like, when you're building with Lovable with an app like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: you have to kind of set up each step, okay? Like, how do I administrate this? How do I do that? And then you just have to kind of build out each of the different pages.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you just have to explain to it, like, the different steps of what you're gonna build. You don't have to understand how it's built, you just tell it what you're needing.
Dorothy: So, when I'm doing the recordings,
Dorothy: Because I've got a mini home studio,
Dorothy: So, where am I putting the recordings onto? Straight into Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's what I just… that's what I just told you, is that you have to tell it to build an admin panel.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To where you would upload the recordings.
Dorothy: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So the place where you upload the recordings doesn't exist yet.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So there's not anywhere, but it has to now… the agent has to then build that into it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That functionality into it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, you would have thought, well, that… that should have been obvious. The agent should have just known to do that. Well, that's the limitation with agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is that oftentimes, they don't necessarily think about the big picture.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it's better that they don't, it's better that they focus on the, kind of, the individual
Jeremiah Krakowski: aspects of that.
Dorothy: Yeah, so you're just building each aspect, and you know that that's been done.
Dorothy: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Not really necessarily building it, you're more telling the tool
Jeremiah Krakowski: What is missing, what's not working, what each aspect is that needs to be… Done.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, let's see, so admin panel, new series…
Dorothy: internal hard drive, so I could just be recording…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Meditation. Okay, here it is. Oh, morning medication. I don't know about medication, but…
Jeremiah Krakowski: We'll do morning medication. Okay, great.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Click the series… Add a session. Okay, here we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So we could do… I don't know how long the session is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Session 1, you can upload the audio files right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So here's an audio file right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: add a session, session added. Now…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the session uploaded, but isn't playing, see? So, you have to kind of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Go through, and it's gonna review, okay, what's… what are the playback issues, all those different types of things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you can either get frustrated with this part of it, or you can kind of, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I find that this is kind of the fun of the process, a little bit.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For me.
Dorothy: Yeah, it's amazing, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: it's not gonna build everything, like, that's gonna be working perfectly right out the gate. I would say building funnels is 10 times easier.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Will do.
Dorothy: Holy…
Jeremiah Krakowski: One of the things that I did, it's giving everybody access to the admin panel.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you don't want that?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you get to tell it, like, okay, I want only certain accounts to have access to the admin panel.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Otherwise, all your users will also be able to access it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, let's see… It says it's playing. Oh, there we go, yep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: educational, informational purposes, not intend to be medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. So now it's playing back the audio that I just uploaded right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But I'm trying to let you know I'm not blowing you off. Yeah, yeah. I can… I understand. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'd love to get… I'd love to get into a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it can… it has the audio that I just uploaded now, right there.
Dorothy: Mmm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a session one.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So right there is kind of like a prototype of this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, okay, the structure of this is a bit off, all members.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm getting admin access, I want to separate those out, so only…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Certain users are admins, others aren't, and clean up…
Jeremiah Krakowski: the interface, so it works better. Review and audit.
Jeremiah Krakowski: everything. This is one prompt I always use. Review and audit everything, and fix any issues.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then it'll just go through everything and kind of fix those issues, and then I'll go back to, like, the next feature that I want to add.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Those are kind of, like, the different ways that you can use agency to make an app like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah. Like…
Dorothy: Very much like working with an administrator.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because you're constantly… you have to go back and say, can you do this, can you do that? It very is… yeah, it is very much like working.
Dorothy: Tweet this.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yep, it's just like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But it usually…
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's gonna add… it'll… overall, it'll take you a lot less time than working with a person.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: because, like, Like, what we just made right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Would have probably taken somebody, like, a week to build.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: at this level.
Dorothy: Absolutely.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We have a… at least a basic… platform.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where we can load sessions into, and then we, you know…
Jeremiah Krakowski: We need a… we need a sales letter on the homepage to sell this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And charge… $7.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a month for it, we'll do Skype integration, edit.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So then, like, that's my… I got queued up message that I gave it. It's gonna have a sales letter, payment, Stripe integration, all that that we can add into it.
Dorothy: No.
Dorothy: And where would you sort of put the price point on audios like this, a sort of audio membership?
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you want to do it free, I guess you could totally do it for free.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah.
Dorothy: I mean, well, I probably would do it as a paid thing, but I'd probably base it slightly on
Dorothy: headspace, and have a look at, you know, what they've done.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They can make it, like, $2 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: $19 a year.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Type of a thing, you know?
Dorothy: How much does, I don't know, well, I'll look up Headspace, and I'll just do some research on that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: cheap at that level. And then you could then use this as a tool to advertise your other type of stuff. So you could, like, okay, put, like, ads every three times that somebody logs in to my yoga studio.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah. Pop up.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, what we have on… Sandy's is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: We have Her Health app, $17 a month. We have over 700 people that signed up for this.
Dorothy: Wow.
Jeremiah Krakowski: put the whole thing in Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Top to bottom.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then, well, I built in Lovable, and then I used Claude Code on my own, and then I used… now I have my agents that are kind of getting in here doing stuff, but it just… it looks beautiful.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so the app, it's over at a realchange.ai.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right here, $17 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So they can chat with it right here, here's the chatbot.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The admin panel is back here. Now, it's not… doesn't load all the right numbers in the back, I need to fix that, it's a little bit of a bug. It's a lot more users that are active than that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because every time you refresh it, the number changes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's just a… that's a bug that I need to fix.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But it's not, like, breaking, because it's not removing people's access, it's just how it's reading the system.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But from here, It gives people access to this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah. And we can ask it questions.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it charges them for the excess.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so we built that into Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Very easily an app, and then what I'm building next is, an Android and an iOS version of those.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, Headspace is… right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Their pricing is $60 a year.
Jeremiah Krakowski: $12 a month.
Dorothy: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: $5 a month discount right there. So you could… you could undercut that down to $20, $30 a year.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or 5… or, you know, $3 to $5 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Something like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, pretty cool, huh?
Dorothy: Yes, very, very cool, thank you, yeah.
Dorothy: Yeah, well, I've got so much material, so yeah, just gotta start doing it, and we'll.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's just kind of… and that's… that's, again, one of the values of, like, having one of these agents set up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Again, yeah, if you guys want me to help you set up one, like the one that makes all those PDFs for me and things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and it just, it's loaded with all your content, things like that, let me know, send me a message on Instagram.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then we can start working together, getting you one of those set up as well.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It'll be the… it'll definitely be a lot more…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm not even necessarily using Lovable or Manus anymore. I'm just using my OpenClaw agents now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because they actually do a better job of everything than those two apps do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like I showed you, it rebuilt in one day, it rebuilt my entire website, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It pulled all the photos, it wrote all the copy, it took all the testimonies.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It just created… a working… website.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for everything that I do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… these are all my blog posts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: These are all the blog posts I've ever done?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you can just scroll through and read them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which I think is pretty cool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If, like, if you go through these, these are a whole masterclass in and of themselves, like this… these blog posts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just everything related to building your business is here on this blog.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I've… I've basically dumped
Jeremiah Krakowski: If I had a podcast on it or taught it in this group, I probably made a blog post about it, too.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So there's 167 posts on there.
Dorothy: And that's all unlovable, is it?
Jeremiah Krakowski: No, this is with my AI agent built this.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: my… my OpenClaw agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I'm rebuilding all of my pages now in here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For my whole website.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Everything.
Dorothy: So, with your blog and with the podcast, do you charge for either of those, or are they both free?
Jeremiah Krakowski: No, they're just free on my website.
Dorothy: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yup.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And now my agents, they're writing better blog posts now, because they're trained on my content, than…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I've ever had written. Like, these are, like, ridiculously good quality blog posts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: on how to… how I'm using OpenClaw and Claude to put everything together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I basically have it listen… like, I'm gonna have my agent listen to this recording of our call today, give me 10 ideas for blog posts, and it's gonna go right to them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so that's… that's how I do my blog post. And then it generates me four versions of, like, an image that I could put at the top here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So… Yep, yep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's… that's what we're… that's where we've moved into as far as the world of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: building our businesses. So now, it's like, I can get my message out there more to more people faster.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Through these different tools.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's great.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alrighty, y'all. Well, it's 3 o'clock, we gotta get going, but…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think this has been eye-opening and informative, and we kind of… we really walked through a lot of different
Jeremiah Krakowski: Use cases and ways to build this stuff out.
Adele Best: Thanks, Jeremiah, it's been really good.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You bet. Let me go look real quick at just what it just did for Dorothy's,
Jeremiah Krakowski: Dorothy's app right here. Okay, great. Here's our…
Jeremiah Krakowski: front end. Stop surviving, start feeling calm. Guided meditation, breathwork.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Chronic fatigue support, all in one simple app.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Build a practice that sticks.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You've tried everything, the apps that feel like homework, the YouTube series with terrible ads.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The advice to just breathe when your body's screaming.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Has the sign-up links right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We'll go to the sign-up page.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So already it's building all this into here.
Dorothy: Amazing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yep. Incredible.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Pretty awesome. Alright, y'all.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Have a good one, and we will talk soon.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Bye-bye.